# ZACKORY KELLY

**FULL-STACK DEVELOPER** 

**②** zackkelly.dev **♀** Toronto, ON **in** zack-kelly **♠** zackorykelly

## **SUMMARY**

Full-Stack Developer with over 2 years of professional experience working in fast-paced start-up environments to deliver effective and reliable software to clients. Strong foundation in all aspects of software development, including ERD and wire-frame design, testing (unit, feature, e2e), Agile and collaborative Git workflow, and more. Knowledge of multiple popular back and front-end frameworks and common APIs and dev tools. Proven communication, adaptability, and teamwork skills with a desire to continue to learn to use new technologies efficiently.

## **SKILLS**

JavaScript, Ruby/Rails, React.js/Next.js, SQL/Postgres, CSS/HTML, Cypress/Jest, Node Express, Storybook, JQuery, TypeScript, Angular, AWS, Data Structures/Algorithms, State Management, RESTful APIs, Python/Django, Node.js

## **EMPLOYMENT**

### RealSage (Formerly Soulrooms Inc) · Full-Stack Developer · Aug. 2021 to Current · Toronto

- Maintain and develop features for a software subscription platform for landlords, using a Next.js/React front-end, TypeScript Node Express back-end, and PSQL database. Work with integrations including AWS, APIs including SendGrid and various leasing management data feeds.
- Design and implement RESTful APIs supported by front end application created using HTML and modern CSS frameworks.
- Oversee the creation of documentation repository to improve team communication and workflow, and reduce bugs and blockers caused by obscurity of infrastructure and legacy code.
- Engage in regular planning and communication with dev and product teams following Agile methodology. Help plan and execute the onboarding of new developers, including coordinating with and managing a remote front-end developer.

#### Chain Champs · Co-Founder, Full-Stack Developer · May 2021 to Current · Toronto

- Work with a small team of tech industry veterans to create and maintain the first NFT marketplace on the WAX blockchain with a live sales feed and price prediction tools for finding the best deals. Develop creation tools to allow community to create collections and host drops on the platform.
- Feature development and maintenance of Angular front-end, API development on TypeScript Express back-end servers and PSQL database. Integrate with smart-contracts on the blockchain for both data storage and transactions.
- Coordinate with data scientist working in Python to maintain prediction models and access the data needed for new features, including the creation of TRUST platform to score crypto wallets and track bot activity using Al and ML.

#### **Self-Employed** · Full-Stack Developer · Jan. 2022 to June 2022 · Toronto

- Worked on a contract basis with a client to create a webapp to advertise and sell a collection of art based NFTs. The collection showcases the Helvetica font in partnership with owner Monotype. Front-end app created using React, React Router, and TailwindCSS.
- Implemented the provided designs with specificity to deliver a responsive and appealing experience on both mobile and desktop.
- Integrated with multiple APIs tied to the Avalanche blockchain, for connecting a user's wallet, accessing NFT data from the chain, and completing transactions using either USD or Crypto. Additional integration for loading image and purchase mapping data from CSV using JavaScript.

# **PROJECTS**

Portfolio Site 2023

- Portfolio site showcasing a number of projects. Includes medium blog integration and contact functionality using captcha and google cloud functions.
- Built using React JS, TailwindCSS, and React Router, and hosted using Google Firebase CLI with additional GCP tools.

JamSpace 2021

- "GitHub for Songwriting" Web app that allows users to create projects and add other users as collaborators. Audio tracks can be recorded in the browser and downloaded, shared, and played back individually, as a group, or even while recording.
- React JS front end using React Router with a Node Express back end. Data is managed using PostgreSQL. Uses Media Streams and Web Audio APIs.

## **EDUCATION**

Lighthouse Labs · Mar. 2021 to June 2021 Diploma Web Development 2021

University of Toronto St. George Campus · Sept. 2010 to Apr. 2015 B.Sc Psychology 2015

#### **Additional Courses**

- Bash Mastery: The Complete Guide to Bash Shell Scripting
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Masterclass
- Learn Firebase Core with React
- Intro to Git